I gotta say,
それにしても 警備ロボの誤動作なんて
having security robots malfunction like this is a real black eye for Antiskill.
警備員の面目丸つぶれじゃん
Still, it was lucky that it didn't become serious.
でも　大事にならなくてよかったです
Hmm, that's weird, all right.
やっぱ変だよな
What's the matter?
どうなさいましたの
Oh, nothing.
いや この警備ロボ　搬入したばかりで まだメインバッテリー入れてなかったんだよ
These security robots were just brought in,
so their main batteries haven't been installed yet.
You mean they don't even have batteries?
バッテリーが入てないだと
That's right. Forget malfunctioning,
はい　誤動作どころか こんなので動くはずがないんですが
they shouldn't even be running at all.
I wonder if there was some residual power in the auxiliary battery.
補助のバッテリーでも残ってたのかな
A blazing hope is blasting through the city
輝く希望が　この街を駆け抜けるから
闪耀光芒的希望 从城市中起跑
いつだって　信じあえる仲間と手を繋ぎながら
无论何时 都与信赖的伙伴们握紧双手
It gives me the strength to hold hands with my trusted friends
心のまま　信じる明日を探し続けてる
相信自己 继续追寻着坚信的未来
and keep looking for a tomorrow that will satisfy us
A Certain Scientific Railgun
立ち尽くす雑踏の中　遠ざかる君を見つめてた
站在繁杂的人群中 找寻身在远方的你的身影
On a crowded street I saw your shape drawing away
Because we understand the love we share now
分かち合うその大切さ　今は分かっているから
分享彼此的珍贵 现在我们已互相了解
smiles light up around me
いくつもの笑顔が　今日も彩って
无数的笑容如今仍明艳动人
and brighten our days
皆を包み込む そんな当たり前を 守りたい
在我身边的那些习以为常 全都想要守护
I want to protect that simple happiness
動き出す夢を　この空に響かせたら
横空出世的梦想 在空中回响
Once my dreams start coming true, with the sky as my witness,
揺ぎ無い力　現実を捉えてゆく
凭借无可撼动的理想 要将现实捕捉
I will begin to have power over my reality
弱さ打ち明ける　そんな強さを持ってたから
拥有能坦诚弱小的强大力量
I had the strength to talk about my fears
いつの日も忘れないよ　この絆だけ抱きしめて
不论何时难以忘怀 拥抱这份羁绊
I won't forget when it was that I did
I will hold dear the bonds that bind us
胸を張って　誇れる未来を撃ち貫いてく
都能充满信心 击穿值得自豪的未来
and blast open a path to a future I can be proud of
Well, guess you can't do anything about it.
そっか　仕方ないね
Yeah, all right.
うん　分かった　それじゃあ
Okay then.
Sounds like Uiharu and Shirai will be a while, checking the scene out and so on.
初春たち　現場検証とか　もうちょっとかかるみたいです
She said we should go on without them.
先に行っててくださいって
Listen, Febri,
ねぇ　フェブリ　これはどう
how about this one?
Wanna trade the pink one for the red one?
そのピンクゲコタ　この赤ゲコタと交換しない
This one is cute too, right? See? See?
こっちも可愛いでしょう　ほらほら
Nope.
嫌だ
Well then, what about together with the blue one?
だからこの青ゲコタも一緒に
Hey! I'll even throw in the yellow Gekota!
エロゲコタもおまけに付けちゃうぞ
This one is mine.
フェブリのゲコタ ゲコタ
The way she's handling this, it really could become hers.
このままじゃ　なし崩し的にこの子の物になっちゃうかも
Out of all the ones I have,
よりにもよって　ひとつしかない貴重なピンクゲコタが
she had to like the one I don't have any duplicates of!
If it has to come to this...
かくなる上は
Oh, Misaka, are you really still at it?
もう　御坂さん　まだやってるんですか
Oh, Misaka...
あら　御坂さん　お帰りですの
Are you leaving?
Hello.
こんにちは
Kongou!
婚後さん
Mitsuko!
光子
Oh, my, you're certainly in good spirits, aren't you?
あらあら　お元気ですわね
You really came through earlier.
さっきは助かったわ
If you hadn't spotted Febri, Kongou,
婚後さんがフェブリを見つけてくれなかったら どうなっていたか
who knows what might've happened?
I really appreciate it.
ホント　ありがとうございました
C'mon Febri, you should thank her, too.
ほら　フェブリもお礼言わなくちゃ
Thank you, Mitsuko!
ありがとう　光子
O-Oh my, a thank you? I only did the right thing.
そ…そんな　お礼なんて わたくし　当然の事をしたまでですわよ
Oh, right. We're headed out for some tea.
そうだ　これから皆でお茶しに行くんだけど
Do you guys wanna come with us?
婚後さんたちも一緒にどう
Wow, have tea together?!
皆でお茶
Ah... As much as I appreciate the invitation,
せっかくのお誘いですけど　まだお手伝いが残っておりますの
I still have work to do around here.
Not at all.
そんな　宜しいのですよ　婚後さん
It's fine, Kongou.
Yeah, we'll take care of the rest ourselves.
後はわたくしたちだけで何とか
What are you talking about?
何を仰るの
Hanging my friends out to dry
お友達のお手伝いを投げ出すなんて
is something that I, Kongou Mitsuko, would never do!
この婚後光子にできるわけありませんわ
Mitsuko! Wanna! Atsuki! Bye-bye!
光子　湾内　泡浮　バイバイ
Enjoy the rest of your day.
ご機嫌よう
Stay safe!
お気を付けて
Yeah!
Well, we should get going then.
さて　わたくしたちも参りましょうか
Huh?
あら
Isn't that...?
あれは
It's so exciting that we can already test the data from the fourth ranked the other day.
先日手に入れた第四位のデータをもう試せるとは ワクワクするね
I would've liked more time to prepare,
どうせならもう少し準備時間が欲しかったけれど
but I guess we can't ask for everything, huh?
贅沢は言ってられないわね
Well now, I wonder what kind of data we'll get this time.
さてさて　今度はどんなデータが得られる事やら
I hope we'll get some entertainment at least,
少しは楽しませてくれるかな
out of Tokiwadai's Railgun.
常盤台の超電磁砲
They even put up the Reach Assembly's posters in here?
こんなとこにも貼ってあったんですね　学究会のポスター
So what did you think, having seen the location?
で　どうだった　実際に会場を見てみて
Though I haven't ever seen it either, so I dunno if I should ask.
っていうあたしも　実は今まで行った事はなかったんだけどね
Hmm, seems like it would be nice,
なんかいいですよね 思い切り打ち込める得意分野があるのって
being able to throw yourself into one specialty.
Maybe I could do some research, too.
あたしも何か研究してみようかな
Like urban legends!
都市伝説の事とか
I dunno about that...
それはどうだろう
Huh? No?
ダメ
Thanks for waiting.
お待たせしました
Oh, here it comes, Febri.
来たよ　フェブリ
Here's your special ice cream.
スペシャルアイスクリームでございます
Aw, you can't eat like that, can you?
それじゃあ　食べられないわね
Guess I'll just have to hold Gekota for you.
仕方ない　あたしがそのゲコタ　預かっといてあげるわよ ほら
Here.
Ah!
Oh, you're so spoiled.
もう　この甘えん坊さん
Here.
はい
Yum!
うまい
Ah!
Sure, sure.
はいはい
Whoo, finally done.
やっと終わったわね
We never really did find out what happened with the security robots.
警備ロボの件は結局原因は分からずじまい
Come to think of it, the traffic light problem had an unknown cause too, huh?
そう言えば昨日の信号トラブルも原因不明でしたわね
Sudden mechanical failure everywhere?
謎の連続トラブルですか
I bet Saten would enjoy such a mystery.
佐天さんが好きそうな話ですね
Yeah.
Hey, do you guys have some time?
ねぇ　二人共時間ある
Is it good?
美味しい
Yeah, I want more.
もっと食べる
Okay, okay.
分かった　分かった
Hello? Oh, Kuroko.
もしもし ああ　黒子
ほら　はい
Huh? Konori?
固法先輩が
You really like this, huh?
ホント　好きですよね
Isn't it great?
いいでしょう　疲れた時はやっぱりこれよ
This is the best when you're tired.
Right, Febri?
ねっ　フェブリちゃん
Febri, this place has a bathtub inside that's this big.
フェブリ　ここってね　こんな大きいお風呂があるんだよ
Let's all have a good time, okay?
皆で一緒に入りましょうね
It'll be fun!
楽しいぞ
そう　夢にまで見たお姉さまとの混浴
Yeah...
I have always dreamed of sharing a bath with Milady.
Just leave it to me!
お任せください　お姉さま
I'll make sure that every last inch of your body is washed clean.
この黒子　お姉さまの体を隅から隅まで綺麗にして差し上げますわ
Every single inch... Every nook and cranny...
隅から隅　そっ　隅の隅まで
Tee-hee
Okay Febri, let's go.
さっ　行くわよ　フェブリ
Yay!
Bath time! Bath time! Bath time!
お風呂　お風呂　お風呂
I-I will not allow my moment of bliss to leave me so easily!
こ…この程度の事で至福の瞬間を逃す訳にはいきませんの
Showtime!
いざ…
Ah, Shirai.
白井　お前も来たのか
You're here too, huh?
Oh...
あれ
That tickles.
くすぐったい
Hey Febri, stop fidgeting.
こら　フェブリ　動かないの
Yeah, there you go!
そう　偉い偉い
Those two are like two peas in a pod, huh?
すっかり仲良しじゃない　あの二人
Yeah, sure are.
ですよね
Isn't this great, Misaka?
よかったですね　御坂さん
Huh?
It's like you have an adorable little sister.
可愛い妹ができて
Oh, what are you talking about?
何言ってるんだか
Little sister, huh?
妹…か
There! All clean, all clean!
ほら　綺麗綺麗
H-Hey, when did you...
あんたいつの間に
Hey Gekota, stop fidgeting.
こら　ゲコタ　動かないの
You think she's imitating Misaka?
御坂さんのマネですかね
She really does make a cute little sister.
ホント可愛い妹だこと
She sure does.
ですよね
That feels good Gekota, right?
ゲコタ　気持ちいいね
There, there, sit still, okay?
よしよし　動かないでね
Good girl, good girl, good girl!
いい子　いい子　いい子
Oh, you're such a good girl!
いい子だね
So Febri, you like Gekota, huh?
ねぇ　フェブリ　ゲコタの事が好き
Yeah, I do!
うん　好き
All right.
そっか　だったらそれ　あんたにあげる
Then in that case, you can keep that one.
Take good care of it, okay?
大事にしてよね　約束よ
Promise?
Yeah! Thank you, Mikoto!
うん　ありがとう　美琴
でもゲコタは元々フェブリのゲコタだよ
But this Gekota has always been mine.
All right, now it's my turn to wash Misaka.
よし　次はあたしが御坂さん　洗ってあげます
In that case, let's all wash each other.
だったら　洗いっこしましょうよ
Isn't this nice?
いいわね
Huh? Not you too, Konori!
Milady... Ah, paradise is just beyond that wall...
お姉さま　ああすぐそこにパラダイスが
The paradise for me alone!
わたくしだけのパラダイスがありますのに
You stopped moving your hands.
手が止まってるぞ
Can't you rub any harder, Shirai?
もっと気合入れて揉まんか　白井
Right...
はーい
Well, I'm headed this way, so...
じゃあ　私はこっちだから
See you tomorrow.
明日も宜しくね
Right, we'll see you later.
はい　失礼します
Good work today!
お疲れ様でした
C'mon, let's go, Kuroko.
ほら　行くわよ　黒子
My bath together...
混浴が　お姉さまとの混浴が
My bath together with Milady...
Why can't we turn back the hands of time?
なぜ時は戻ってくれないのですの
Kuroko, what are you doing?
黒子　なにしてんの
Ruiko...
涙子
Okay, okay.
はいはい
Getting you all warmed up made you sleepy, huh?
暖まって眠くなっちゃたんですね
Looks like your back has become reserved seating,
すっかり指定席になっちゃたわよ
huh, Saten?
佐天さんの背中
But that'll all be over in five more days.
でも　それも後五日で終わりなんですね
And after we've become such good friends, too.
せっかく仲良くなったのにな
Well it's not like we'll never see her again.
もう　会えなくなる訳じゃないんですから
Don't feel lonesome for her, Milady.
寂しくなるんじゃありませんの　お姉さま
I-I wasn't planning on it.
あ…あたしは別に
Gekota...
ゲコタ
Well, maybe a little.
まぁ　ちょっとだけね
Once Febri gets to Asunaro Park, let's all go visit her together.
フェブリちゃんがあすなろ園に行ったら 皆で会いに行きましょうよ
Yeah, sure!
そうね でも　今度はゲコタ人形とられないようにしなくちゃ
But this time, I'll have to be careful not to let my Gekotas get stolen.
Oh, come on, Misaka!
もう　御坂さんったら
What's the big deal? You have so many of them!
いいじゃありませんの　沢山お持ちですし
You say that like getting them is easy!
ちょっと　そんな簡単にとれないんだから
Sidewalk
Closed
Huh? We can't cross here?
あれ　渡れないの
Oh well, guess we'll cross at the next one.
仕方ありませんね　もう一本先を渡りましょう
Detour
Really?
こっちもですの
Detour
Here too, huh?
It's quite a long way around,
大分遠回りですけど　工事ですから　仕方ないですね
but since there's construction, we don't have much of a choice.
What a pain.
めんどくさいな
Huh?
あれ
We can't get through here, can we?
迂回　できませんわね
This is where the detour said to go, right?
ちゃんと迂回路通りにきましたよね
I thought we did.
のはずだけど
I'll check my GPS.
ナビで調べてみますね
Huh? Kongou tried to call me.
今後さんから着信が
Kongou Mitsuko?
婚後光子から
Oh, me too.
こっちも こんなに
Whoa, this many?
Must've been right when we were bathing, so we didn't notice.
丁度お風呂に入ってて　気づかなかったみたいですね
I wonder if it's something urgent.
何か急用だったのかな
What was that?
何
Now, let the experiment begin.
さぁ　実験開始です
#20 "Febri"
A Certain
Scientific Railgun
S
Huh?
Get back!
下がって
Misaka!
御坂さん
I don't know
どこの誰だか知らないけど
who you are,
but did you think something like this would work against me?!
こんなもの　あたしに通用するとでも思ってんの
Milady!
お姉さま
Kuroko! Keep out of this!
黒子　手　出さないで
Misaka!
御坂さん
I'm unable to control it?
このあたしが操れない
It's not using shields or anything. For that matter,
シールドとかじゃない
っていうか　そもそも電気系統そのものが存在しない
it doesn't have any electrical systems at all!
Just like the simulations. Well then, next up...
シミュレーション通りだね
それじゃあ　次は
How is it moving?
なんで動けるの
I'm not sure what's going on here,
よくわかんないけど
but from the looks of it, someone's inside.
見た感じ　人が中に入ってるタイプよね
Jeez, what a pain in the neck!
ったく　めんどくさい
Crap!
やばっ　佐天さん
Saten!
佐天さん
Uiharu, contact Antiskill!
初春　警備員に連絡を
All right!
分かりました
H-How come?!
何…何で
What's the matter?
どうしたんですの
The call won't go through!
携帯が繋がらなんです
Huh? What do you mean?
どういう事
Febri!
フェブリ
Hey, this is dangerous, you know?
ちょっと　危ないでしょう
What're you doing? Come on, quickly!
何やってんの　ほら　早く
What's the matter?!
どうしたんだ
It stopped...
動きが
どっせい
That's about as good as you'll fare when confronted with me!
わたくしにかかれば　ざっとこんなものですわ
Kongou!
婚後さん
What are you doing here?
どうしてあなたがここに
Wherever Kongou's friends are, there I shall be!
お友達あるところ　婚後ありですわ
But never mind that, what's going on here?
それより　何事ですの　これは
Yeah.
そうだ　どこのどいつがこんなマネを
Who on earth would pull something like this?
What is this?
何　これ
It's empty?
空っぽ
What's going on?
どういう事
Febri!
フェブリ
What's the matter?! Wake up!
どうしたの　しっかりして
Febri!
フェブリ
This was within our assumptions.
これも想定内さ
Sure enough, our calculations were correct.
やはり　僕たちの計算は正解だよ
Febri! Are you all right?! Febri!
フェブリ　大丈夫　フェブリ
I-Is she hurt anywhere?
ど…どこか怪我でも
C-Call an ambulance!
救…救急車を
But our cell phones aren't—
しかし携帯は
It's going through now?
電波が通じいてる
Then please hurry and call someone!
だったら早く連絡してください
R-Right, will do.
はいですの
You guys again?
またお前たちか
I wish you could have seen it!
お見せしたかったですわ このわたくしの大活躍
My heroic exploits! When the robot was closing in,
迫りくるロボットをちぎっては投げ…
I plucked it up and tossed it.
Plucked it right up and tossed it!
So no pilot and no battery.
搭乗者もバッテリーもなし
We don't know what's going on here,
昼間の警備ロボと同じで　訳が分からんじゃんよ
but it's the same as it was with the security bots.
It's true! If you check the security cameras around here,
ホントなんです　このあたりの監視カメラを調べてもらえば　分かりますから
you'll see it.
It's not that I doubt you.
別にお前らを疑ってるわけじゃないじゃん
But none of the cameras recorded anything out of the ordinary.
けど　どの監視カメラの映像も 何も異常は記録されてないじゃんよ
None of them?
監視カメラが
Come to think of it, our cell phones weren't working before just now, either.
そう言えば救急車を呼ぶ前も　携帯が繋がらなくて
For the time being, leave this up to us.
とりあえずここはうちら任せろ
But...
でも
Your friend was taken to the hospital, right?
友達が病院に運ばれたんだろう
Go and see her.
早く行ってやるじゃん
All right. Uiharu...
分かりました　初春
Right.
はい
Okay then.
それでは
Yeah.
C'mon now, what's going on here?
ったく　何がどうなってるんじゃん
Here we go.
What is this?
なんだ
Mizuho Systems Hospital
Yeah.
Yeah, all right. Bye.
わかった　じゃあね
Kuroko says they'll be here shortly.
黒子たちも　もう少ししたらくるって
It didn't look like she had any injuries.
怪我とかもしてなかったみたいだし
She's gonna be fine, right?
大丈夫ですよね　フェブリ
For crying out loud, worrying all of us like this...
まったく　みんなに心配かけて
Once she wakes up, I'll be like, "What's the big idea?"
目が覚めたら　どうしてくれよ
Febri!
フェブリ
Doctor, uh...
先生　あの
Her fever hasn't gone down,
発熱が収まらず　依然意識も戻りません
and she still hasn't regained consciousness.
I don't know why her condition is worsening,
病態悪化の原因もわからないし
and to be honest, I'm stumped.
正直お手上げです
Anyway, there's not much more we can do for her here.
とにかく　ここじゃあ　手の施しようがありません
We need to move her to a larger hospital right away.
至急　もっと大きな病院に搬送します
Febri...
フェブリ
This is yours, right? Hold onto it.
あんたのでしょう　しっかり持ってなさい
We now know that our research works more than well enough against Railgun.
我々の研究は　超電磁砲に充分通用する事が分かった
It's a shame that the experiment was stopped that way, though.
ああいう形で実験が中断されたのは　残念だったけど
Guess that's just what happens, huh?
飼い犬に手を噛まれるとは　この事だね
But with today's data, the program will be even more accurate.
でも　今日のデータで　プログラムはより精度が上がるわ
Indeed, all thanks to the great rank three.
まさに第三位さまさまだよ
We've also now demonstrated one more thing...
これでまた一つ証明された
The incapability of those who must rely on their abilities.
能力に頼らざるを得ない連中の無能さがね
This indeed is the great inconsistency of Academy City.
これこそ　学園都市の矛盾だよ
Now then, let's take a vote.
さて　ここで一つ決を採ろう
This is concerning Febri's disposition.
フェブリの処置についてだが
This is taking a while, huh?
時間　かかってますね
Then again, what was that thing?
でも　何だったんでしょう　あれ
If that thing hadn't shown up, Febri wouldn't be this way...
あんなのがこなければ　フェブリだって　こんな
I don't know who these guys are,
どこの誰だか分からないけど
but it came after me.
あれは　あたしを狙って来た
It's because of me...
あたしのせいで
Once again,
また　誰かを巻き込んじゃった
someone else got dragged into it.
Milady?
お姉さま
Kuroko! Uiharu!
黒子　初春さん
How's Febri doing?
フェブリちゃんがどうですか
Well, we don't know yet.
それが　まだ
Really?
そうですか
How about you?
そっちは
Oh, Antiskill ended up taking over the investigation.
はい　警備員が引き続き調査する事になりました
But as of now, we don't have any leads.
けど　今のところ　手がかりらしきものは何も
By the way,
ところで
why did you follow us here?!
どうしてあなたが付いてきてるんですの
Why? Because I'm worried about Febri, of course!
どうしてって　フェブリちゃんの事が心配だからに決まってますわ
Looks like you helped us out again, huh? Thanks, Kongou.
また助けてもらっちゃったわね
ありがとう　婚後さん
Oh, by the way, you tried to call us earlier.
そう言えば　さっき電話をくれたみたいだけど
That's right!
そうですわ
There's something I wanted to tell you all.
わたくし　皆さんにお知らせしたくて
There's danger closing in on Febri!
フェブリちゃんに危険が迫っているって
Earlier, I noticed a man near the Reach Assembly location.
先程　学究会の会場近くで見知った男を見かけましたの
But then...
そうしたら
That's...
あれは
What do you plan to do?
何をするつもりですの
I just want to have a word with him.
ちょっと　あの方とお話するだけですわ
He seems to have gotten the wrong idea about you, Kongou.
婚後さんがどんな方か誤解なさっているようですから
Yeah, I'm sure if we spoke to him, he'd understand.
そうですね　話せばきっと分かっていただけますわ
Huh? But...
The target is on the move. Right.
ターゲットは移動中だ
そうだな　フェブリ回収に失敗したが
We may have failed to retrieve Febri,
but imagine, getting such a surprise.
こんな副産物があったとはね
Hmm? Yeah, send them my way, please.
こっちに回してくれ　頼むよ
We should be able to obtain some interesting results.
興味深い結果が得られそうだ
Febri was being targeted?
フェブリが狙われてる
But we couldn't reach any of you.
ですが　皆さん全然連絡が取れなくて
We had no choice but to split up and look for you,
仕方ありませんので　手分けして探しておりましたら　偶然
when, by chance—
Hang on just a sec, okay?
ちょっと失礼しますわね
Hello? Oh, Wannai and Awatsuki!
もしもし　湾内さん　泡浮さんも
Oh, I'm so sorry. I completely forgot to call you two.
ごめんなさい　お二人へ連絡するのすっかり忘れておりました
Yes, I managed to find Misaka and the others.
御坂さんたちとは会えましたわ フェブリちゃんも　ですが
Febri too, however...
Huh? Me? I'm fine.
わたくし わたくしは大丈夫ですわよ
Those two must be worried about you.
お二人共心配されてるのでしょう
We're fine here.
こちらは大丈夫ですの
I'll have none of that!
そうはいきませんわ
Oh, sorry. I wasn't talking to you.
すみません　こちらの事で
You must be exhausted after searching for so long.
お二人はずっと探してくださって　お疲れでしょうから
Oh, no! That's fine, I'll come to you!
いえ　それならわたくしがそちらに行きますわ
No, really, you don't need to worry.
そんな　ホントですから　どうかご安心なさって
Well, then.
では　申し訳ございませんが　わたくしはこれで
I hate to be leaving, but I need to go.
でも　何かありましたら　教えてくださいね
But if anything comes up, please tell me, okay?
Febri is our friend too, after all.
わたくしたちもフェブリちゃんのお友達ですから
Yeah, thanks.
ありがとう
What does it mean, you think?
さっきの話　どういう事でしょう
Recovering Febri? What on earth?
フェブリ回収って　一体何が
"Recovering," even. Febri isn't a thing.
回収だなんて　フェブリは物じゃないのに
Ladies.
君たち
Febri!
フェブリ
Ah, Mikoto!
美琴
Are you okay, Febri?
大丈夫なの　フェブリ
Hmm? Okay?
大丈夫
Febri, you collapsed all of a sudden, and we were so worried about you.
フェブリちゃん　急に倒れちゃって
皆心配してたんですよ
Gekota, are you okay?
ゲコタ　大丈夫
Huh?
Apparently, you're just fine, huh?
どうやら元気なようですわね
Hmm?
You have a minute?
ちょっといいかな
Are you sure it doesn't hurt anywhere?
痛いとことかホントにないの
It doesn't hurt!
痛くない
Thank goodness!
Okay.
そっかそっか
Um, thank you very much.
あの　ありがとうございました
Not at all. I didn't do anything.
いや　僕は何もしていないね
Huh? But...
だって
I'm not able to fix her up, y'see.
僕にはあの子を治せないからね
Fix her up? What do you mean?
治せないって　どういう事ですか
You don't mean she has something more serious, do you?
まさか　重い病気とか
No, but if she had some human illness, I could cure her.
いや　人の病気なら治せるんだけどね
But, that girl isn't a human at all.
あの子は　人間じゃない
She is a hundred percent scientifically created
百パーセント科学的に作られた
artificial construction.
人造物だよ
A Certain
Scientific Railgun S
S
Huh?
I walked through our town,
君を知ったこの街は　私には広すぎて
你所熟悉的这个小镇 对我来说有些宽广
but it was too big for me
I tried to hide my discomfort,
焦り不安ごまかして　強がり背伸びした
慌忙来掩盖自己内心的不安 逞强着故作平静
made myself a little taller and pretended to be strong
I got an answer that puzzled me,
見つからない答えに　心は浮かんだまま
对于无法找寻的回答 心中对此怀抱幻想
and everything became complicated
息つぐ暇もなく　時は流れる
在我屏住呼吸的一瞬 时光匆匆流逝
and everything became complicated
My daily life has given me trouble,
繰り返す日常に　苦しくなったなら
对于日复一日的生活 感到痛苦的时候
深呼吸一つして　ほら
就深呼一口气 看吧
but I'll take a deep breath
Above that hill
虹さす　丘の上　目指していこう
向着山丘上那一道彩虹 朝着那里奋斗
I see a rainbow
Let's go find it
I will make sure I will never forget this day
忘れない　今日も刻んでいく
将难以忘怀的今天铭记在心
I'm so happy
出会えたことに　ありがとう
为相遇而心存感谢
I could meet you
It will always be special
きっと　大事だね
一定是很重要的
It will always be special
Let's be proud and walk forward
前を向いて　歩きだそう
向着前方 迈步前进
Our happiness will be our link to tomorrow
明日につなげる笑え合えたね　ありがとう
用彼此的微笑串联明天 心存感谢
When you share
喜びも　悲しみも 分かち合って
不论喜乐哀愁 都要彼此分享
When you share
your happiness and your pain,
さあ　重ねてゆこう
来 一起前进吧
it's twice the fun and half the pain
Next Episode
Preview
Me? Doing the preview?
わたくしが予告だなんて
#21 "Darkness"
I only did what any friend would do! I was worried about Febri!
お友達として　当然の事をしたまでですのに
フェブリちゃんが心配ですわ
Next time, Kongou saves the world!
次回　婚後航空　世界の旅
Oh no you do not!
違いますの